live like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother James
yes sir and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage Thou shalt
have no other gods before me Thou shalt
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my commands
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man's servant nor thy maid servant
nor thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in them is and resteth the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill
Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal th Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's wife
nor as man's servant nor as maid servant
nor as Ox nor as ass nor anything that
is thy neighbors I read Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsil to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
the questions that we will not answer
are vague and long scripture questions
as well as questions of debate we are
not here to debate we are here to spread
the true Gospel of God so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program also
remember that this is a live stream so
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life we just ask
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
to you to family that's on the panel
this evening we got brother Dre good
evening brother Julius good evening
everybody brother
Jerome rest and peace brother James good
evening everyone sister Deborah good
evening brother
Sean good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening yes there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into uh
tonight's
Q&A the job related as is there a
precept for Jude verse 9 is this
mentioned elsewhere in the
Bible all right is there a precept for
Jude verse 9 that last book before
Revelations let's go there brother James
yes sir I'm
there and read that verse 9 and the
guest caller will take it from
there Jude verse
9 Yet Michael the Archangel when
contending with the devil he disputed
about the body of Moses D not bring
against him a railing accusation but
said the Lord rebuke
thee okay all this all this really
saying is that uh you should not
be you don't speak evil of anything or
anybody Michael could have raised the
whole lot of Cain with the uh uh uh with
Satan because Michael can handle Satan
however Michael hit him with the big
thing he said the Lord rebuke thee and
that's enough back up and read verse
eight we're going to have a look at this
we going to read verse eight
first likewise likewise also these
filthy dreamers defile the flesh despise
dominion and speak evil of
dignities now see this is and this what
what he's saying how how people are
always uh speaking evil of dignity and
always speaking about things they don't
know and uh bringing real acquisition
against
somebody and when and then it use
Michael as an example he only said the
Lord rebuke thee to say Satan skip down
to verse 10 read verse 10 and
11 but the speak evil of those things
which they know not but what they know
naturally as brute beasts and those
things they corrupt themselves woe unto
woe unto them for they have gone in the
way of Cain and ran greedily after the
era of baim for reward and perished in
the gain saying of core
this talking about people that's always
running their mouth and talking evil you
know and and accusing somebody now let's
go into
Matthews 5th chapter read verse
33-37 okay Matthew 5: 3 through 37 says
again ye have heard that it has been
said by them of old time Thou shalt not
forear thyself but sh perform unto the
Lord thine oath but I say unto you swear
not at all neither by heaven for it is
God's Throne nor by the Earth for it is
his foot stol neither by Jerusalem for
it is the city of the great king neither
shalt thou swear by thine head because
thou cast not make one hair white or
black but let your communication be yay
yay
nay nay or whatsoever is more than these
cometh of
evil so he saying is don't be so quick
to run your mouth accuse people and make
accusation and swear about stuff that
you can't
control you just answer the question or
speak to the situation at hand just like
it was and Michael and
Satan because God is the one that buried
Moses no nobody else buried him because
Moses went up into the mountain and he
died there so it's obvious that the Lord
did buried him and Michael and Angel
Michael and Satan was uh disputing over
his body and all Michael said was the
Lord rebuke thee he didn't have to call
you low down dragon with your sin and
self and your this and that and a whole
lot of bunch of unary uhuh no he just
say what need to be said that's why he
said Michael make no wild acquisition he
just say simply the Lord rebuke thee and
this is simply saying that you shouldn't
speak evil of anything good or evil or
just run your mouth without having a a
reason to that's all I have to
say all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we
continue to move on to our next one
moving on philosophy asked in Luke 5: 3
6 through
39 what is the meaning of this
Parable all right the parable in Luke 5
verse
36-39 let's go there brother James and
when you get there read that and the
guest caller will take it from there
okay Luke 5:
36-39 says and he spake also a parable
unto them no man putteth a piece of a
new garment upon an old if otherwise
then both the new maketh the rent and
the piece that was taken out of the new
agree not with the old and no man
putteth new wine into Old bottles else
the new wine will burst the bottles and
be spilled and the bottles Shall Perish
but new wine must be put into new
bottles and both are preserved no man
also having drunk old wine straightway
desireth new for he saith the old is
better okay this and this particular
thing all Jesus is doing is just
condemning a man-made
tradition back up and read verse 33 and
34 because this way verse
33 verse 33 says and they said unto him
why do the Disciples of John fast often
and make prayers and likewise the
Disciples of the Pharisees but dine eat
and
drink so now they want to ask the
question why is it that you ain't doing
the same thing that the disciples did
John disciples and the
Pharisees because these are Traditions
that people did read the next verse and
he said unto them can ye make the
children of the Bride chamber fast while
the bridegroom is with them
so it's telling you why is it that she
we should follow this fasting uh uh
tradition when the bridegroom is with
them you know when I leave they can fast
but it was a tradition they would they
had traditions and those Traditions
sometime made the the word of God to
have no effect now let's go into First
Matthew the 15th chapter and we're going
to read from 1 to n 15
1-9 okay Matthew 15: 1-9 says then came
to Jesus scribes and Pharisees which
were of Jerusalem saying why do thy
disciples transgress the tradition of
the elders for they wash not their hands
when they eat
bread this what we getting that's what
we getting off in the tradition you
understand the tradition of the elders
but they wash not their hand before they
eat bread in other words it was it
wasn't just hand wash it was a whole lot
of washing and stuff they did before
they ate because they had tradition but
what did Jesus ask them say to them go
ahead but he answered and said unto them
why do ye also transgress the
Commandment of God by your
tradition for God commanded saying honor
thy father and mother and he that
curseth father or mother let him die the
death but ye say but ye say whosoever
shall say to his father or his mother it
is a gift by whatsoever thou mightest be
profited by
me and honor not his father or his
mother he shall be free thus have ye
made the Commandment of God of none
effect by your
tradition and this and this what Jesus
was was talking about that's why he said
why why is that you want to put new wine
in the old bottle or either so a new
patch on a old garment you know it's
it's it's uh some things don't fit you
got all these Traditions like washing
and carrying on that Israel did and John
the Baptist people they did the same
thing but when Jesus came along they
weren't fasting or none of that stuff
they come through they eating and they
drinking wine and everything else and
that was a tradition that was uh uh uh
contrary to fasting but Jesus said hey
when I
go then they have time to grieve and
fast and all
that so all there was about was
Traditions why should you use tradition
because sometimes
tradition in a lot of cases make the
word of God to have no effect by your
tradition that's all I have to say all
right thank you for that hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next moving on Willie Tate says the
story of king herod's massacre of Hebrew
babies is generally considered fictional
by historians where can I find this in
the history books in a lesson Tau by iog
so I can take notes on this all right we
know some truth in that and we know it
happened brother Julius what you got I
got three sources I got the number one
source in the world the word of God the
Bible
listen in Matthew the 2 chapter I
have my own set of encyclopedias this is
kers this is K's encyclopedia up under
the Herod the Great up under the haod
the great this right here K's
encyclopedia upon the Herod the Great
also I have world's Book Encyclopedia
Volume 11 volume 9 which is Herod the
Great I have uh there's another book
that's called Herod the Great by uh by
uh Mr
Green but we got the more sure word of
Prophecy let's go to Jeremiah the 31st
chapter let's do this quick James
because we gotta read do a little bit of
reading because fiction
means false made up imagine imagine
nonfiction means
true Jeremiah 31 and just give me verse
15 thus sayth the Lord a voice was heard
in Rama lamentation and bitter weeping
Rahel weeping for her children refused
to be comforted for her children because
they were not this is Rachel it says
right here but it's Rachel weeping for
her children but she refused to be
confident Rachel represents Israel the
nation Israel weeping for her children
because she was not they were not why
because they was executed by Herod the
Great now let's go to Matthew the second
chapter and let's put this piece
together okay Herod was an aduman King a
mad man and paranoid killed everything
that was threatened to uh that was
threatened to his throne when they said
that a a child was going to be born he
wanted to kill Jesus yep Matthew 2 pick
it up at verse 7 real quick go ahead
then Herod when he had privately called
the wise men inquired of them diligently
what time the star appeared go ahead and
he sent them to Bethlehem and said go
and search diligently for the young
child and when ye have found him bring
me word again that I may come and
worship him also no he want to kill
Jesus get down to verse 12 quickly and
continue and being warned of God in a
dream that they should not return to
Herod they departed into their own
country another way so now skip down to
verse 16 and read it then then Herod
when he saw that he was mocked of the
wise men was exceedingly wroth and sent
forth and slew all the children that
were in Bethlehem and in all the coast
thereof from two years old and under
according to the time which he had
diligently inquired of the wise men so
now why did this have to happen read the
next verse go ahead then was fulfilled
that which was spoken by Jeremy the
prophet saying in r was there a voice
heard lamentation and weeping and great
mourning Rachel weeping for her children
and would not be comforted because they
are not so now what happened when Herod
was
dead verse 19 but when Herod was dead
behold an angel of the Lord appeared in
a dream to Joseph in Egypt saying arise
and take the young child and his mother
and go into the land of Israel for they
are dead which sought the young child's
life so now while he was alive and old
Herod tried to kill Jesus when he found
out that a king was going to be born but
the angel said go down in Egypt until
Herod is dead and it said everybody is
dead that seek a young child's life I'm
going show you how fictional this that
this is is on your own go and look up
the slaughter of the Innocence the
slaughter of the Innocence on your own
and it will show you it is so important
the Lord had this thing had the Catholic
Church believed it because they put a
date on it it is called December the 28
and it is called the day of the
Innocence and it falls every year on
every year on December 28th it can fall
on any day but the date is always
December the 28th anybody can Google
this the date of the slaughter of the
innocent and look up the slaughter of
the Genesis and you will find out that
it is a day that the Romans set up in
honor of the slaughter of the Innocents
all the people that hero here so this is
not fiction it is nonfiction it's in the
Bible it is prophecy it is true no
matter what historians said the let the
word of God be true Romans 3 and4 let
the word of God be true and every man of
Li that's all I got on
that all right thank you for that bright
light there brother as we move on to our
next question next one Doc Martin have
two questions she
says if a family member died can we go
to the
Cemetary and also were July and August
added to the 12 month calendar or just
renamed all right so first question
Julie if a family member died can we go
to the cemetery yes you can go to the
cemetery the body got to be buried the
body got to be prep and you go to the
cemetery what you can't do is you can't
touch the body but you can go to the
cemetery let's go and look at somebody
who that Jesus tomb let's go to St John
the 20th chapter at his
Seer St John chapter 20 and verse one
James when you get it St John 20 and
verse one okay the first day of the week
cometh Mary Magdalene early when it was
yet dark unto the Sela and seeth the
stone taken away from the slia now
that's a cave or either place where a
body is
put a a body is put but who else came
also you can read the whole thing on
your own read verse six go ahead then
cometh Simon Peter following him and
went into the Sela and seeth the linen
clothes lie so he actually went into
Jesus Seer where he was buried at and
saw with a linen lie so you go to the
cemetery but you can't touch the body
okay so they got they got funeral people
that do that but here's uh the answer
what's the second question uh
Debbie were July and August added to the
12 month calendar or just
renamed they were all renamed jly and uh
well the July is named after Julius
Caesar as a reward the Romans allowed
him to uh they renamed the month of um
quintillus which is the Roman original
name of it was quintillus which we call
July was named after Julius Caesar and
then August was renamed uh the original
name was sex tillers but it was renamed
August after Julius Caesar's nephew
Augustus Caesar so but the Romans in the
original Roman Calendar they had two
months the two months that was had 10
months I'm sorry but two months was
added January and February was
added and that made 12 months but God
has always had 12 months
so July and August was renamed they were
already there but January and February
was added by the Romans to make up 12
months that's all I
got yes sir and um like you said brother
Julius they can go to the cemetery but
they unclean for seven days hey that's
what the book say numbers and 19 on your
own you can read it yep all right thank
you for that brother as we move on to
our next question next question K Le ask
are the askanazi
Jews and do they know who we
are do they know who we are brother
Jerome uh yeah when you talk about do
they know um who we
are you know that's I couldn't tell you
from one individual to another whether
they know who we are but um the askinazi
Jews they are the
um um but people refer to them
as as canaz
Jews because they pretty much name
themselves after the the land of the
Gentiles who and who was called
ashkanazi Because the actual
ashkanazi are Gentiles
Europeans and the were in the
land of Ashkenazi which belong to the
Gentiles okay but let's go to uh Genesis
the 10th
chapter I'm there and read verse 1
through3 and then skip to five
okay now these are the generations of
the sons of Noah shim ham and japat and
unto them were Sons born After the flood
the sons of J japheth Goomer and magod
and midad and Javan and tubal and meach
and Tyrus and the sons of Gomer ashkenaz
and Riad and togar
by verse that's what came that's where
you get the word ash kazes from this uh
name Ash canaz in verse three and he's a
son of japat and japat is the
progenta of the Gentiles or we call
commonly call white people go ahead and
finish that verse five by these were the
aisles of the Gentiles divided in their
lands everyone after his tongue after
their families in their
Nations yeah
now the actual
Edomite which is the twin brother of
Jacob you know his father is Isaac just
like
Jacob you know his father is Isaac so
they Brothers they twin brothers okay so
let's go trace him through the scripture
let's go to 1 Chronicles the first
chapter
and pick it up at verse 24 read to
27 and we gonna skip verse 24 shim
aapad sha Eber pag R serak nahor Tera
Abram the same as
Abraham the sons of Abra that's good
okay so I just wanted to trace you from
shim to Abraham let you know that
Abraham traced Jem now skip down to
verse 34 and pick up Abraham
again and Abraham begat Isaac the sons
of Isaac Esau and Israel yeah and Esau
that's that's the Edomite which they
call asazi Jew but that's the Edomite he
the twin brother of Israel whose name
who Jacob whose name was changed to
Israel and Isaac is his father he a
Hebrew he just not a Hebrew Israelite he
not a gentile out that's all I got
on all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered their question as we
move on to our next moving on Clara
Maloy says if Gentiles can make the
first resurrection is it wrong to pray
over my children that they would also be
a great nation of Kings and Priests and
she gives Revelation 1: 5 5 and 6
Revelations 20 verse 6 and Galatians 3
verse 29 and she says would you consider
them a part of the great
nation all right so dealing with the
Gentiles making the resurrection you
went over our two scripture maximum by
one but we going to be nice today guess
caller go read all the script
Revelation 1 5
and6 okay Revelation 1 5 and6 says and
from Jesus Christ who is the faithful
witness and the first begotten of the
dead and the prince of the kings of the
earth unto him that loved us and washed
us from our sins in his own blood and ha
made us Kings and Priests unto God and
his father to him be glory and Dominion
forever and ever
amen go to the next one okay Revelation
says blessed and holy is he that haveth
part in the First Resurrection on such
the second death have no power but they
shall be Priests of God and of Christ
and shall reign with him a thousand
years and gal galatian 3 and 29 says and
if ye be Christ then are ye Abraham's
seed and HS according to the
promise well okay so all of them uh all
of them are talking about the
resurrection what you talking about
praying that your children be a great
nation I'm going tell you what you
should pray for you better pray that
your children uh uh uh uh uh be in any
Resurrection on the right side of the
Kingdom because this is what the Lord
said let's go into uh uh St
John I'm sorry St Matthew 19th Chapter
vers 16 and
17 this what you don't have to pray to
your children be this what you do is you
teach your children this so they will
get eternal
life Matthews 1916 And1
17 okay Matthew 19:16 and 17 17 says and
behold one came and said unto him good
Master what good thing shall I do that I
may have eternal life and he said unto
him why callest thou me good there is
none good but one that is God but if
thou will enter into life keep the
Commandments right so now you praying
for your children to be Kings and
Priests you should be teaching your
children the king keep God's
Commandments as far as the Gentiles
concerned why shouldn't the Gentiles yet
be in the resurrection if they do
everything that God if they obey the
same word that God gave
Israel because when he get to
Resurrection come to the
resurrection and serving God correctly
that
transcend uh uh race and nationality now
let's go back to Galatians the 3 chapter
that you went and we're going to start
read this up at from 26 to 29 now okay
Galatians 3:
26-29 says for ye are all the children
of God by faith in Christ Jesus for as
many of you as have been baptized into
Christ have put on Christ there is
neither Jew nor Greek there is neither
Bond nor free there is neither male nor
female for ye are all one in Christ
Jesus and if ye be Christ then are ye
Abraham's seed and HS according to the
promise so now if you going to get into
God get that promise and get into God's
kingdom that transcends race color
gender a nationality that's why I said
there's neither a Jew nor Greek male nor
female if you be Christ then Abraham
seed and air according to the promise so
now if you GNA get in the first
resurrection let's go look at it and see
what the Bible said about the first
resurrection let's go into Revelation
the fth chapter we're going to read
verse
one and we going to skip down to verse
five and we're going to skip and read
from verse 8 to 10 Revelation 5 And1
first revelation 5 And1 says and I saw
in the right hand of him that sat on the
throne a book written within and on the
backside sealed with Seven
Seals okay and and and what happened was
could
nobody remove the seal that open that
book with Jesus get down to verse five
you know because John started the weep
and the angel and and and and the Lord
told him to weep not we got one that can
open this book verse five verse five
says and one of the elders saith unto me
weep not Behold The Lion of the the
tribe of Judah the root of David had
prevailed to open the book and to loose
the Seven Seals
thereof and the book he's talking about
is the Bible people think it that's just
but some different book no this book is
from uh uh Genesis the Revelation and
Jesus is the one that revealed it to us
nobody else till now the line of the
tribe of Judah is Jesus now skip
down the verse 8 and continue from 8 to
10 go ahead and when he had taken the
book The Four beast and four and 20
Elders fell down before the lamb having
every one of them Harps and golden vows
full of oders which are the prayers of
saints and they sung a new song saying
Thou Art Worthy to take the book and to
open the seals thereof for thou was
slain and has redeemed us to God by thy
blood out of every Kindred and tongue
and people and nation and has made us
unto our God Kings and Priests and we
shall reign on the
earth so not the only
people so the people that's going to be
Kings and Priests and going to rule this
Earth with Jesus are the people that was
uh that was Redeemed by his blood these
are the people going to make the are the
people in the first resurrection now
Gentiles going to be in the first
resurrection because it says out of
every Kendrick nation in tongue so those
are the Saints that's going to run this
earth and the only Kingdom the only
Kingdom and of and with priests and
Kings is is going to be Jesus Kingdom
they're the only one that's going to run
it your children ain't going to be no
nation and they ain't going to be no
great nation if they be anything at all
if they get in the first resurrection
they will be a part of the only
nation that's going to run this Earth
which is led by let's go into Zechariah
the 9th chapter and read verses 9 and
10 okay
[Music]
Zachariah the 11th chapter in verses 9
and
10 nth chapter nin chapter
okay Zechariah 9:9 and10 says Rejoice
greatly oh Daughter of Zion shout out oh
shout oh daughter of Jerusalem Behold
thy King cometh unto thee he is just and
having salvation lowly and riding upon
an ass and upon a coat the fo of an ass
and I and I will cut off The Chariot
from Ephraim and the horse from
Jerusalem and the B bow shall be cut off
and he shall speak peace unto the
Heathen and his Dominion shall be from
sea even to Sea and from the river even
to the ends of the
Earth so now that is going to be the
only Kingdom on this
Earth so uh it ain't going to be no
great Nations or nothing it's going to
be the kingdom of Jesus it's all that
simple do now if you kids getting the
first resurrection then they will be a
part of the people that will help Jesus
run this great Kingdom which is his
kingdom that's all I have to say all
right thank you for that hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next question brother canel before
we go before we go into further my
question for will he take verse for
number three does the Israel God have a
lesson on Herod the Great uh we got the
upcoming black history series part one
and part two coming up in February also
we have a lesson world history told by
the prophets look those up thank you all
right and
Israel and Israel replaced by and Jacob
replaced by his brother Esau thank you
yep all right I hope you take note of
that as we move on to our next question
moving on hidden Israel says I'm in the
process of obtaining land that I can
lease out for billboard advertis
advertising should I lease out my land
for this use if some of these companies
May advertise ungodly things and pagan
holidays well I would suggest that you
um do your homework because if you're
going to lease out your land you should
have an idea what it is that they want
to be advertising let's go into uh
Psalms the 14th chapter let's say this
this is one of the things that they want
to advertise but you want that up on
your land Psalm
14 and when you get there
brother I want you to pick it up at that
verse one because if it's your land and
you rent it out you got a right to know
what is it that you want to put up on
that sign on my
land now if he put this up there I would
have an issue with it verse one go ahead
bro the fool has said in his heart heart
there is no God they are corrupt they
have done abominable works there is none
that doeth good now what if somebody
want to put that on that sign even
though you leasing out the land that
there is no God or put up something
abominable up there and you know that
you stand on something totally different
which is the word of God go ahead read
the Lord looked down from the heaven
upon the children of men to see if there
were any that did understand and seek
God they all they are all gone aside
they are all together become filthy
there is none that doeth good know not
one because there's a lot of things that
are being put that are against God and
you don't want that up on full
advertisement if you have a choice as to
what can go up on your own property now
turn over to uh first Thessalonians the
5th chapter chapter for me
okay okay when you get there just read
um 22 and 23 for me
because for you to be a Christian and
claiming that and somebody know that you
okay for something to go up that's
totally abominable and against God verse
22 abstain from all appearance of
evil and the Very God of Peace sanctify
you holy and I pray God your whole
spirit and soul and body be preserved
blameless until the coming of our Lord
Jesus Christ yeah so just let your light
shine and just be careful you know ask
them uh what is it they want to put up
there beforehand and then you make the
decision because uh there some stuff
that people are putting up that should
not be and that's all I got on
that all all right we hope that answered
your question as we move on with the
time check to our next one yes the time
is
811 malici Shakur ask is there a prayer
I can say if someone is constantly
bothering and harassing me at work
constantly being bothered and harass at
work is there a prayer what you say
Dre yes sir um you know what when when
you I think about that the let's go to
Romans the 12th
chapter because we got to have our minds
right so when the harassment come you
know how to deal with it you put your
trust in the most high God make sure you
not late for work and you ain't CAU up
in something and and if you if you if
you in good standing and doing what you
called to do you know just keep pressing
on but but let's look at we gonna answer
that question
Romans 12 verse 7 read that
brother or Ministry let us wait on our
ministry or he Romans Romans 12 verse
7 that Romans 12 verse S verse 17 okay
yes sir no problem recompense to no man
evil for evil provide things honest in
the sight of all men
uhhuh if it be possible as much as lith
in you live peaceably with all
men dearly beloved avenge not yourselves
but rather give Place unto wrath for it
is written vengeance is mine I will
repay sayeth the Lord the Lord will if
you just standing right if you not in
the position where you wrong cuz if
you're wrong it's going to come to you
and it's something that we deserve but
if you not
wrong let's look at this let's go to
uh let's go to uh uh Psalm 7 Psalm
7 okay I just want to read one verse
there Psalm 7 and the first verse Psalm
7 and one oh Lord my God in thee do I
put my trust save me from all them that
persecute me and Deliver Me So from the
heart reach the heart when you praying
to the Lord and it's from your heart and
you gonna trust in him he will deliver
you but you got to be in right standing
too I got one other place let's go to
Psalm 70 Psalm
70 Psalm 70 pick it up at one go ahead
brother 70 and one
says make haste oh God to deliver me
make haste to help me oh Lord mhm let
them be ashamed and confounded that seek
after my soul let them be turned
backward and put to confusion that
desire My
hurt yes sir let let them be turned back
for a reward of their shame that say aha
aha let all those that seek thee rejoice
and be glad in thee and let such as love
thy salvation say continually let God be
magnified that's the that's a good
prayer there are some prayers where you
where David said fight against those
that fight against me and do them some
harm but what you want is peace of mind
at your job and while you at that job
you you do your job and seek some peace
and pray to the Lord for it and he'll
give it to you just wait patiently on
him and make sure that you doing what
you called to do that's all I got on
that can we read that verse five too
brother Drake go ahead
brother but I am poor and needy make
haste unto me oh God Thou Art my help
and my deliverer oh Lord make no
tearing right
yeah we
on the Lord that's it rely on he will
deliver you y yep that is true all right
brother thank you for them scripts hope
that answer a question as we move on to
our next next one miss way says in Luke
16 verse 8 please explain wiser than the
children of light who are
they all right weits want to know who
are the that are wiser than the children
are light who are they let's go to Luke
16 when you get there brother read that
verse eight guest caller will take it
from
there Luke Luke 16:8 says and the Lord
commanded the unjust Steward because he
had done wisely for the children of this
world for the children of this world are
in their generation wiser than the
children of
light okayness that's talking about in
the evil doing you know I just I just
thought about it if somebody could cuz
you had something on this order or uh I
think it's in Ezekiel when it's talking
about Satan when he says wiser than
Daniel can somebody pull it up right
quick uh
e three 28 and
three 28 what
start at verse right start at verse one
then okay Ezekiel 28 And1 says the word
of the Lord came again unto me saying
son of man say unto the prince of Tyrus
thus sayith the Lord God because thine
heart is lifted up and thou has said I
am a God I sit in the seed of God in the
midst of the Seas yet thou art a man and
not God though thou set thine heart as
the heart of God he said you're a man
but not God but he but he is talking
through behind the man keep reading what
did he say behold Thou Art wiser than
Daniel there is no secret that thy that
they can hide from
thee now so he's talking actually to the
one that's behind the King which is
Satan the devil he is wiser okay Daniel
is a
uh is is a children children was a a
Child of Light he knew the truth now
even though Satan was was wiser than
Daniel he's wiser to do evil and he
going to end up in the Lake of Fire same
thing with people here so but this whole
thing was Jesus let you know that this
guy is wiser than Daniel wiser than the
uh the children of light because he know
how to recover
let's go into Luke the 16th chapter and
read 1- 4 first okay Luke 16: 1 through
4 says and he said also unto his
disciples there was a certain rich man
which had a steward and the same was
accused unto him that he had wasted his
goods and he called him and said unto
him how is it that I hear this of thee
give an account of thy stewardship for
thou May be no longer Steward then the
steward said within himself what shall I
do for my lord taketh away from me the
stewardship I cannot dig to beg I am
ashamed I am resolved what to do that
when I am put out of the stewardship
they may receive me into their
houses so now this guy is saying look
I'm going to go out and I'm going to
make some deals
so now cuz I can't I can't won't be able
to be steid don't know how to work and I
can't beg so I'm going go out and I'm
going to make some deals with who with
the wicked skip down to verse verse uh
uh uh8 now and read that verse again and
go into verse n okay um Luke 16: 8-9
says and the Lord commanded the unjust
Steward because he had done wisely for
the children of this world are in their
generation wiser than the children of
light and I say unto
you go ahead and I say unto you make to
yourselves friends friends of the Mammon
of
unrighteousness that when ye fail that
may they may receive you into
Everlasting
habitations now but they but you don't
want to be in their habitation so now
what does it mean wiser than the
children of like he's
wiser in in doing
evil because the Lord said look he's
letting you know right here what this is
letting you know is if you ain't going
to serve God then you may as well get
the best of the living you can on this
Earth skip down to verse
13 no servant can serve two masters for
either he shall hate the one and love
the other or else he will to the one and
despise the other ye cannot serve God
and
Mammon so now this Steward here if we
keep reading this Steward went out and
made a deal with all the people that
owed him
money and he and uh uh he maneuvered so
being that he knew that he was not going
to he couldn't serve God didn't want to
serve God so what he did he went out and
served mmama so he went and got as much
as he can like a lot of people get rich
in this world but they ain't going to
get uh into the kingdom of God the good
side of the Kingdom they are
wiser than the children of light in that
they are wise to do
evil but when it come to wise of eternal
life then they ain't so wise because
they going to end up in the Lake of Fire
they wiser do
evil that's all I have to say all right
so make sure you don't get your foot
caught in that trapped there all right
we hope that answered your question as
we move on to our next one moving on
commissioner Paula a Sanford asks what
would happen with the elderly and
disabled who are in nursing homes when
it's time to go to the Wilderness so
what's going to happen to them when it's
time to go to the
Wilderness all right Julius what you got
to say about this merciful God we serve
I know one thing when when Egypt left uh
when Israel left Egypt the Lord I'm sure
they had the elderly and the poor and
the sick and the Lord didn't leave none
of them he didn't leave none of them
there and you could uh you could go back
to the scriptures and read that well uh
he left with 600,000 they were just
footman but let's go to Isaiah the 46th
chapter 600,000 left Egypt was nobody of
Israel left in Egypt no Isaiah 46
brother
James and we just got one verse there
and then we gonna go one more place
Isaiah 46 and
verse4 now what happened to the elderly
same thing that can happen to the
elderly when it's time to go to the
Wilderness you don't need no passport
you don't need no money the matter of
fact the Lord will use people to take
you to the Wilderness go ahead and for
and even to your old age I am he and
even to hairs will I carry you go
ahead I have I have made and I will bear
even I will carry and will deliver you
so he GNA deliver you you got WID not
understanding he gonna make sure that
you have everything that you need to get
to the Wilderness one more place let's
go to 1 Corinthians chapter
10 1 Corinthians chapter
10 okay
and we going to read verse 13 there 1
Corinthians 10 and 13 when you get it my
brother James go ahead and read there
has no temptation taken you but such as
is common to man yes but God is faithful
who will not suffer you to be tempted
above that ye are able but will with the
Temptation also make a way to escape
that ye may be able to Bear it now you
got wisd knowledge and understanding the
Lord going to make sure and you sering
him he already done gave you the signs
he done told you when to flee he done
told you where to flee to in the
wilderness so he going to deliver on
your own go back and read that Psalms
The 91st chapter you know he going gonna
get his angels and he going to deliver
he going to protect you in the
wilderness and wherever you are because
he told you I will never leave you nor
forsake you I'mma Be A little Sanctuary
to you
so I trust him and I trust his word
that's all I got brother
Cornel yes sir indeed he is
merciful all right hope that answered
your question there we move on to our
next one moving on be alert as does the
scripture State how long the
will resume animal sacrifice before they
are stopped how long will the
be doing sacrifice before it's put to a
stop brother
Jerome well I definitely don't want you
to be confused about the practicing of
sacrificing that that you may see them
do from time to time it's got to be a
daily sacrifice and once they start to
do it daily then the verse we use to uh
determine how long they're going to be
doing it is in the eighth chapter of
Daniels and we're going to tie with the
uh 12th chapter okay go to Daniels the
8th
chapter and read verse um 13 and
14 okay Daniel 8 verse 13- 14 says then
I heard one Saint speaking and another
Saint said unto that certain Saint would
spake how long shall be the vision
concerning the daily sacrifice and the
transgression of desolation
to give both the sanctuary and the host
to be trotten
underfoot and he said unto me until
2,300 days then shall then shall the
sanctuary be
cleansed okay now a a figure is given in
the 12th chapter as to this daily
sacrificing being stopped and we're GNA
subtract the
2300 um figure from this figure we
getting ready to read in the 12th
chapter and that'll give you give you
the amount of days that they're going to
do the daily sacrifice okay so go to
that 12th chapter and read verse
okay Daniel 12:11 says and from the time
that the daily sacrifice shall be taken
away and the Abomination that maketh
desolate set up there shall be a,2
190 days yeah so you you subtracted
2300 from the
1,290 and that'll give you
1,10 days and that's how long long they
going to be doing the daily sacrifice
before it stop that's all I got
on all right that was some good light
there brother thank you hope that answer
day question as we move on to our next
next one Trisha Israel of God asked are
the sudanes
hamites are the sudanes hamites brother
Julius yes they
are let's go to Genesis the 10th
chapter I'm I'm
there Sudan is on the African
continents and it is below
Egypt Genesis 10 my brother and read
verse six just verse six Genesis 10 and
verse
6 and the sons of ham Kush and misim and
put and
Canaan now Kush is modern day
Sudan misraim is modern day
Egypt put is modern day Libya and Canaan
is the holy land today so uh the sudanit
are indeed hamites we are scattered
among them but St color but two
different nations another less another
story all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question moving on debor Wilder asks for
you to explain John 13 vers 7 and 8 and
11 through
15 all right John 13 7-8 and then 11-15
need a little light shed on that brother
Dre what you say let's go and read that
um read it when you get there brother
James that is again chapter John 13 yep
seven through seven and 8 okay 11- 15
okay Jesus answered and said unto him
what I do thou knowest not now but Thou
shalt know
Hereafter see what what I'm doing you
don't know what I'm doing but you're
going to know Hereafter go ahead Peter
saith unto him Thou shalt never wash my
feet Jesus answered him if I wash thee
not thou H has no part with me so in
other words it's Jesus that's gonna wash
us with the washing of the
word that word and then with the baptism
and what he did in the sacrificing of
himself but skip down to verse 11 go
ahead for he knew who should betray him
therefore said he ye are not all clean
so this clean he talking about is not
just the foot washing this got to do
with being cleansed go ahead so after he
had washed their feet and had taken his
garments and was set down again he said
unto them know ye what I have done to
you ye call me master and Lord and ye
say well for so am so I
am if I then your lord if I then your
Lord and Master have washed your feet ye
also ought to wash one another's feet
uhuh for I for I have given you an
example that ye should do as I have done
to you so he gave us an
example that we should
do as he have done to us in other words
walk in humility because the foot
washing is one thing but then what Jesus
did was he he gave us a word to live by
and if we are walking in him we should
do the same we should be in example of
that word and we should give others that
same word to live by preach the gospel
that's it I hope that helps yep that's
correct brother Dr because the Lord say
he didn't come to be served but to serve
didn't he yes sir brother all right
brother thank you for that hope that
answered their question sister Deborah
time check as we go to our next yes uh
the time is
8:32 we are now in
we're going into where New Territory
right yes we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday January the 15
2025 Mr ah says can you explain John 1
verse1 17 Grace and Truth what does
grace mean is there a full lesson on
this all right well one we're going to
say that Grace is a free gift something
that we needed because all have seen
that com short of the glory of God so we
needed God Jesus to come and die and
give us that free gift so we can have
access back to the tree of life but as
far as you're asking about a full lesson
yeah we do have a lesson called Grace a
free gift retained by keeping the law
Grace a free gift retained by keeping
the law now let's go in that John 1
brother James John
one and let's pick it up at that verse
one and see who we dealing with here
because the word here is the one that
came to die for the sins of the whole
world go ahead
brother in the beginning was the word
and the Word was with God and the Word
was
God the same was in the beginning with
God go ahead all things were made by him
and without him was not anything made
that was made uhhuh in him was life and
the life was the light of men yeah so
all things were made by him that's the
same one that came to die for the sins
of the whole world all things were made
by him and in him was life and the life
was the light of men so we know that
Jesus came bearing that truth so you
asked about that truth this is the one
that came bearing it because he told us
that his father sent him to come and do
the same skip down and read verse
17 for the law was given by Moses but
Grace and Truth came by Jesus Christ
yeah so the law was given by Moses he's
the one that came and let it be known
everything that Jesus had said and how
we supposed to keep the Commandments and
walk in the laws and statutes and
Commandments but we still needed that
Grace we still needed that blood of
Jesus to come and die for the S of the
whole world now what did John the
Baptist say in verse 29 go ahead the
next day John seeth Jesus coming unto
him and saith Behold the Lamb of God
which taketh away the sin of the world
yeah so we we all needed that we needed
that Grace for him to come and die so he
could take away our sins so that we may
straighten up and fly right so to speak
now let's go into second Peter 1 second
Peter
1 because this is the book that people
try and kick against and it's not
possible second Peter
1 and let's pick it up brother at that
verse
one go ahead
Simon Peter a servant and Apostle of
Jesus Christ to them ha that have
obtained like Precious Faith with us
through the righteousness of God and our
Savior Jesus Christ that truth is
righteousness teaches us how to walk go
ahead Grace and peace be multiplied unto
you through the knowledge of God and of
Jesus our lord uhhuh according as his
divine power hath given unto us all
things that pertain unto life and
godliness through the knowledge of him
that hath called us to glory and virtue
because the Lord came and opened that
door and said hey he is coming to
recruit people to be in the god family
now skip down and read verse 20 and 21
because this is what a lot of people try
and kick against and it's simply not
possible cuz when you say that a man
wrote this book hey you giving him
credit that is not even to be spoken of
he's not that smart all the people on
the Earth put together could have put
together such a great book read 20 and
21 knowing this first that no Prophecy
of the scripture is of any private
interpretation for the prophecy came not
in all time by the will of man but holy
men of God spake as they were moov by
the Holy Ghost and that is how the truth
was brought to us we had holy men that
the Lord shared the word with them or
with us and hey and the Holy Ghost was
right there to make sure that this word
was written so that no man can get
around it they can pretend but they
don't have it that's all I
got yes go right ahead
sir input on it let's cuz I want to I'm
gonna give it directly the way it says
now okay go back to John the first
chapter and read that 17th
verse okay John John 1 and 17
says for the law was given by Moses but
Grace and Truth came by Jesus
Christ okay now we need to Def find this
this particular law that was given by
Moses because people think that this is
the law God's Royal law but it's not
talking about that law let's go to
Hebrews theen show you what La is
talking about Hebrews 10
And1 Hebrews 10 and one says for the law
having a shadow of good things to come
and not the very image of the things
that things can never with those
sacrifices which they offered years by
year continually make the comers there
unto
perfect now the only person that's
perfect is God do now of animal
sacrifice that they sacrifice for
sin you couldn't become God you couldn't
you you you uh uh uh you couldn't be
made perfect why is that skip down to
verse four and read it for it is not
possible that the blood of bulls and of
goats should take away sins so that was
the whole thing is as long as you this L
animal sacrifice couldn't take away sin
you could not be saved you could not
become God but J Jesus came and gave you
a free
gift verse
five wherefore when he cometh unto the
world he saith sacrifice and offering
thou wouldest not but a body has thou
prepared me now so now being that Jesus
was G and he couldn't die he needed a
body so Lord prepared this body so being
that the sacrifice of the animals
couldn't help you Jesus needed something
that could be sacrificed so let's see
what happened with that body skip down
to verse 10 and go ahead by the which
will we are Sanctified through the
offering of the body of Jesus Christ
once for
all now that's what he needed a body for
so we could be set apart and
Sanctified with his death keep reading
and every priest standeth daily
ministering and offering often times the
same sacrifices which can never take
away
sins uhuh but this man after he had
offered one sacrifice for sins forever
set down on the right hand of God from
hence for from henceforth expecting till
his enemies be made his foot stol who is
for by one offering he had perfected
forever them that are
Sanctified so now when he made that
offering that was a free gift there
ain't nothing that man did that Jesus
come and die
for so but we was under the law of
animal sacrifice Moses G gave us that LW
but Jesus when he came and died for us
he is the one that gave us the grace the
free gift that we could
become Immortals again so what he did
was he gave himself something that the
animals couldn't that's all I have to
say all right thank you for that and um
I stand in correction for that the law
that was given by Moses it was animal
sacrifice thank you for that add on hope
that answered your question and you give
us a time check as we move on to the
next yes the time is
8:41 Zion says while the Saints are on
while the Saints are in the wilderness
for three and a half years before Jesus
comes who will we be there
with all right so are the Saints are in
the wilderness for the three and a half
years before Jesus comes who will we be
there with guest caller
well let's go back and see who was with
Israel when it was in the wilderness the
first time as go to Exodus the 203 Chap
and read verse
20 okay Exodus
23:20
says behold I send an angel before thee
to keep thee in the way and to bring
thee into the place which I have
prepared oh so it was an angel he sent
to do that so now that was when the
Israel went into Wilderness the first
time that angel protected him and did
everything that he need to do now this
last Wilderness when we go let's see
who's going to be there let's go into
Psalms chapter 91 yes
sir we're going to read one and three
one to three okay Psalm 91: 1 through3
he that dwelleth in the secret place of
the most high shall abide under under
the shadow of the
Almighty I will say I will say of the
Lord he is my refuge and my Fortress my
God in him will I
trust surely surely he shall deliver
thee From The Snare of the Fowler and
from the noisome
pestilence now how is he going to do
that skip down and read verse
11 for he shall give his angels charge
over thee to keep thee in all thy
ways it was like it was in the first
Wilderness when we come out of Egypt it
was the angel there that kic that that
took us and kept us in the way and so we
go to the Wilderness this last time you
going to have the Angels there to
protect us if you had read through find
out a you going only see what's going to
happen to the rest of the world but they
ain't going to shoot one bullet over
there or drop one bomb cuz them Angel
going to protect you the same way the
angel protect in Israel in the first
Wilderness that our forefathers went
to I
see yeah amen L Lord say only with your
eyes will you behold the reward of the
wicked when you in that
Wilderness all
right thank you for that I hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next one next one rose Martin asks
is Jesus God the father in Exodus
24:
9-1 all right it's two in a godhead we
know that but let's go to Exodus 24 9-11
and let's open this up to the P after
brother James read that go ahead brother
then went up Moses and Aaron naab and
abue and the and 70 of the Elders of
Israel and they saw the god of Israel
and there was under his feet as it were
a pave work of a sapphire stone and as
it were the body of Heaven in its
clearness and upon the Nobles of the
children of Israel he laid not his hand
also they saw God and did eat and
drink all right
panel now let's go to uh St John 1
and8
yep okay St John 1 1 and 18
says no man has seen God at any time the
only begotten son which is in the bosom
of the father he hath declared him yep
the cas then who do they see go to First
Corinthians the 10th chapter start
reading at verse one 1 Corinthians 10
and 1 says moreover Brethren I would not
that ye should be ignorant how that all
our fathers were under the cloud and all
passed through the sea and were Bap all
baptized unto Moses in the cloud and in
the sea and did all eat the same
spiritual meat and did all drink the
same spiritual drink for they drank of
that spiritual rock that followed them
and that rock was
Christ oh so then that was Jesus back
there with Moses and all of them Jesus
the one that brought the Red Sea but to
be sure that you don't misunderstand us
let's go to one other place St John
537 St
John
5 and 37
[Music]
says and the father himself which has
sent me have borne witness of me ye have
neither heard his voice at any time nor
seen his shape
okay the 74 Elders they saw
Jesus so Jesus Is God just like the
father is God that's all have to say
that's right hey brother James that's
some airtight light right there ain't it
yes sir all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one next one Andrew asks what does it
mean by for charity shall cover the
multitude of sins
ver uh scripture 1 1 Peter 4 ver8 is
given charity shall cover a multitude of
sins many sins in 1 Peter 4 and8 brother
Jerome what you
say yeah let's go read it 1 Peter 4
and8 1 Peter 4 and8 says and above all
things have fervent charity among
yourselves for charity shall cover the
multitude of
sins yes charity in this verse is simply
keeping the Commandments of God you know
you love God with all your heart mind
soul and strength and you love your
neighbor as yourself and that's the
charity he that he referring to all
right let's go to um 1 Corinthians
chapter
13 okay and read verse
3-8 1: 3-8
says sorry about that says and though I
bestow all my goods to feed the poor and
though I give my body to be burned and
have not charity it profiteth me nothing
charity suffereth long and is kind
charity envieth not Charity B bth not
itself it is not puffed up
doeth not behave itself unseemly seeketh
not her own is not easily provoked
thinketh no
evil Rejoice not in iniquity but rejoice
in the truth beareth all things
believeth all things hopeth all things
endureth all things charity never
faileth but whether there be prophecies
they shall fall mean shall fail whether
there be tongues they shall cease
whether there be knowledge it shall
vanish away for we
know Skip down to the 14th chapter and
read verse one and that that's all I got
okay follow after charity and desireth
spiritual gifts but rather that ye may
prophesy yeah so keep simply keep the
Commandments of God love God with all
your heart and love your neighbor that's
all I got on y yep brother Jerome you
love God then your neighbor go get some
love too yes sir all right brother thank
you for that hope that answered that
question and let's move on to our next
question sister with a Time Check Yes
the time is
8:50
NR says I understood that the time to go
to the Wilderness is when the pope takes
residency in the temple
but it seems that Daniel 12 verse1 is
saying that it it's when the daily
sacrifice is ended is the sequence of
events the pop will end the daily
sacrifice and then he will move to the
temple yeah sound like they hitting it
right on the head but let's open this
question up to the panel let's go to
Daniel 12
okay I'm Daniel 12 and when we get there
read that verse
11 and go ahead my brother and from the
time that the daily sacrifice shall be
taken away and the Abomination that
maketh desolate set up there shall be
1,290
days yeah brother Jerome dealt with that
a little bit earlier on how long they
going to do them sacrifices and let's
open it up to the panel because they
want to know that they understood sister
Deb read that question again yes the
question is he wants to know about the
sequence uh will it be is a sequence of
events the pope will end the daily
sacrifice and then he will move to the
temple open to the
P well when you read Daniel it said it
really tell you from the time that the
David sacrifices set up and the
Abomination is taken away and the
Abomination set up that mean time he get
there he's going to stop it
yeah yeah that is that is the answer
right
there speak for
itself y all right so sister Deborah
let's um move on to our next question
there open it up to the panel because
time is flying when you're having fun
yes the next question we can talk right
here says I'm
confused has the Son of God been on
Earth before was he King
MDC and was he
Jesus all right has the Son of God been
on Earth before is he M kedc and is he
what Jesus yes open to the P he's all of
that that was him in the Garden of
Eden we answered that earlyer ain't
nobody ever seen the father at any time
or seen his shape that was in St John
5:37 that mean yeah God was Jesus uh uh
in the Garden of
Eden as Jesus is mesc because he is the
high priest that's right and the show
you Hebrews the 7th chapter and start
reading at verse
one okay Hebrews
7 and verse one says for this
melchisedek king of Salem priest of the
most high God who met Abraham returning
from the slaughter of the Kings and
blessed him to whom also Abraham gave a
tenth part of all first being by
interpret ation king of righteousness
and after that also king of Salem which
is king of
peace without father without mother
without descent having neither beginning
of days nor end of life but made like
unto the Son of God abideth a priest
continually now so now being it the only
way you can get out of the priesthood is
to die to the mesed de couldn't die
could he NOP NOP no that's why when he
came there with Jesus so Jesus Lo his
priesthood to Levi for a minute but he
had to take of a flesh and blood body
that could die but when he rose back he
was a Mor again then he picked up his
priesthood again that's why I tell you
have a high priest over the over the
household of God which is Jesus so yeah
he was on Earth in the Garden of Eden he
was on earth when he walked among Israel
when he told them when they use the
washroom dig a hole and cover it up
because the Lord didn't want to an
unclean thing to put it in our language
he didn't want to step in your
crap right but when Israel but when
Israel sinned against God and made a
calf while Moses was in the mountain
that's when the Lord said look I'm not
going to go up among you no more I'm
going to send my angel among you unless
I break out and kill all of y'all that's
when Moses had to get the Tabernacle of
the congregation and said it a way away
from the camp because the Lord was
actually
there so yeah he been on
Earth he's the one that told you in
Exodus 25th chapter build me a
tabernacle so I can dwell among you
that's exactly what he did
yeah yeah same one that came and died
for all our
sins that is correct yes yes sir all
right hope that answered your question
there sister Deborah we down to our last
question or two what is our next one all
right um Trisha Israel of God asks
what's the rule for how long should thou
wait to go back to church after thou has
attended a
funeral so how long should it be to go
back to church after you have attended a
funeral
yes
carer but being that we not in the
temple see you got to understand
something we are in a unclean
land we have a touch with toilets in
it and the first time somebody go in
there start use the toilet to building
is polluted so we don't even try to
enforce that law we have to wait until
we get back to the land and the Lord can
put that back and order but right now
what's what's clean and what's
holy so what are you protected when you
go to a feral then then you can go right
on back to
class everything polluted
anyway all right we're going to move on
to our next question as time is a ticket
yes next question uh Zion says wasn't
Jesus risen an early Sunday
morning open to the panel what you say
Julius of course not
no you can't get three days and three
nights from Friday to Sunday
morning go to St John the 20th chapter
and start reading at verse one yes sir
yep that's it 20 and verse John 20 and
verse one says the first day of the week
coming Mary Magdalene early when it was
yet dark unto the Suppa and seeth the
stone taketh away from the
sea then then she runneth and cometh to
Simon Peter and to the other disciple
whom Jesus loved and Sai unto them they
have taken away the Lord out of the
supplier and we know not where they have
laid them laid
him so now when they got to the Suba
early the first day of the week which is
called Sunday he was
gone yep Jesus rose on the Sabbath day
just before
Sundown which is
Saturday that is correct
yep all right sister Deborah our final
question of the evening all right uh
jiger
Israel ass in Genesis 18
verse1 and Genesis 18 verse
33 was this Jesus In the
Flesh all right let's go to Genesis 18
And1 that brother I'm read that one and
at 33 and they want to know is this
Jesus In the Flesh we open up to the
panel for our last question of the even
Genesis 18 And1 says and the Lord
appeared unto him in the plains of
mammory and he set in the tent Door In
the Heat of the day so we know he
appeared unto Abraham skip down to verse
33 go ahead and the Lord went his way as
soon as he had left communion with
Abraham and Abraham returned unto his
place question was
deer was this Jesus In the
Flesh panel guess
called no he wasn't in the flesh he was
in the spirit but he could take the form
of anybody that's
right two angels that he came down when
he brought with him when he was uh at
that time going to destroy Sodom and gar
they thought they was men but they was
not flesh they were Spirit beings he
couldn't come in the flesh until the
body was made for
him
right y so
you still a spirit B but a spirit B can
take any kind of
shape y that is right all right we want
to thank everybody from all around the
world who tuned in with us this evening
we thank you thank you for those
questions and we had fun answering them
for you but we say that if you submitted
a question we didn't have a chance to
get to it please do not resubmit a
question because we will take it and put
it in rotation
for next Wednesday so sister Deborah
will do that for us so don't resubmit
your question and until we all come
together again please be safe be blessed
stay prayerful and may the Lord have
mercy on us all as brother James closes
herself Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our debts as we forgive
our debors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen amen